Arthur J. Finkelstein Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Consultant File, 1970-2015 (Box 1-62)
  - Nano, Fatos See Container 52, Partia Socialiste e Shqipërisë (political party: Albania) (Box 41)
  - Nassau County Republican Committee, 1984-1986 See also Container 40, Margiotta, Joe; See also Container 41, Mondello, Joe, 1984-1990 (Box 41)
  - National Citizens Coalition, 1983-1987 See also Container 5, Brown, Colin, (6 folders) (Box 42)
  - National Citizens Coalition, 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 43)
  - National Congressional Club See also Container 25, Helms, Jesse (Box 43)
    - Direct mail, 1984-1989 (Box 43)
    - Funderburk, David, 1985-1986 (Box 43)
    - General, 1979-1991, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Hendon v. North Carolina State Board of Elections, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Koehler, Judy, 1985-1986 For additional material see also Container 32, Koehler, Judy (Box 43)
    - Media, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Miscellany, 1985-1987 (Box 44)
    - News clippings, 1983-1986, (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - Surveys/polls, 1983-1988 (Box 44)
  - National Conservative Foundation (Box 44)
    - Campaign management school, 1981-1986, 1981-1987 (Box 44)
    - General, 1983-1989, (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - National Conservative Political Action Committee (NCPAC) See also Container 76, Dolan, John Terrance ("Terry") (Box 45)
    - Candidate training seminar, 1983-1989 (Box 45)
    - Direct mail, 1986-1987 (Box 45)
    - Executive briefing packet, 1986-1987 (Box 45)
    - General, 1983-1988, (2 folders) (Box 45)
    - Independent expenditures, 1981-1982 (Box 45)
    - Independent expenditures, 1981-1982 (Box 46)
    - Information booklet, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Legislative profiles, circa 1986 (Box 46)
    - Media (Box 46)
      - State totals, 1982 (Box 46)
      - Survey, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Political reports, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Project '88, 1985, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Surveys/polls, 1981-1987, (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Surveys/polls, 1981-1987 (Box 47)
  - National Endowment for the Preservation of Liberty, 1986-1988 (Box 47)
  - National Republican Congressional Committee (NRCC) (Box 47)
    - Congressional accountability report, 1985 (Box 47)
    - General, 1980-1988 (Box 47)
    - Post-election surveys, 1976, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Survey research bulletin, 1984 (Box 47)
    - Survey summaries, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Tracking program, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Vote totals, 1986 (Box 48)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee (NRSC) (Box 48)
    - Coalitions calendar of events, 1988 (Box 48)
    - Election update, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
    - General file, 1980, 1984-1991 (Box 48)
    - Illinois poll, 1985 (Box 48)
    - Inner Circle, 1985 (Box 48)
  - New York Post, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - New York Post, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - Nickles, Don (U.S. Senate, Okla.) (Box 49)
    - Direct mail, 1986 (Box 49)
    - General, 1986-1989 (Box 49)
    - Legislative history, 1983-1986 (Box 49)
    - McCarville Report, 1981, 1985-1986 (Box 49)
    - Media (Box 49)
      - Advertisements, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 49)
      - Finances, 1986, (5 folders) (Box 50)
      - Proposals, 1986 (Box 50)
      - Proposals, 1986 (Box 51)
    - News clippings, 1985-1987, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Opposition research, 1986 (Box 51)
    - Surveys/polls, 1983-1986, (3 folders) (Box 51)
  - North Carolina Congressional Club See Container 43, National Congressional Club (Box 52)
  - Noto, Anthony See Container 60, Suffolk County Republican Committee (Box 52)
  - O'Shea, Lester, 1985-1989, (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Pataki, George (Governor, N.Y.), 1994-2005, (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Partia Socialiste e Shqipërisë (political party: Albania), 2005-2007, 2011 (Box 52)
  - Partia Socialiste e Shqipërisë (political party: Albania), digital files, 2005-2007, 2011, mss86414_221_011
  - Pressler, Larry (U.S. Senate, S.Dak.), 1987-1989 (Box 52)
  - Pressler, Larry (U.S. Senate, S.Dak.), 1987-1989, (2 folder) (Box 53)
  - Pylpyshyn, Viktor (Mayor, Kiev, Ukraine), 2008 (Box 53)
  - Quinn, Robert P. (U.S. House of Representatives, N.Y. Third Congressional District), 1984-1985, (3 folders) (Box 53)
  - Raese, John (Governor, W.Va.), 1986-1988 (Box 53)
  - Raese, John (Governor, W.Va.), 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Rama, Edi See Container 52, Partia Socialiste e Shqipërisë (political party: Albania) (Box 54)
  - Republican National Committee, 1978-1985, (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - Republican National Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 55)
  - Republican Party of Texas, 1982-1984, 1972-1984 (Box 55)
  - The Reserve Fund, 1981-1985, (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - Ress, William (State Senate, Ohio Thirteeth District), 1984 (Box 55)
  - Rettaliata, Toni (Town supervisor, Huntington, N.Y.), 1987 For additional material see Container 40, Margiotta, Joseph (Box 55)
  - Rich, Frank D., Jr. (U.S. House of Representatives, Conn. Fourth Congressional District), 1987 (Box 55)
  - Rich, Frank D., Jr. (U.S. House of Representatives, Conn. Fourth Congressional District), 1987 (Box 56)
  - Richard Quinn and Associates (South Carolina), 1981-1983 (Box 56)
  - Rogozin, Dmitry (President, Russia), 2008 (Box 56)
  - Romano, Neil (U.S. House of Representatives, N.J. Ninth Congressional District), 1984 (Box 56)
  - Sanders, Kent (State Senate, N.Y.), 1982-1984 (Box 56)
  - Schaus, Nicholas (U.S. House of Representatives, Conn. Sixth Congressional District), 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - Scott, Tom (State Senate, Conn.), 1987 For additional material see Container 45, National Conservative Political Action Committee (Box 56)
  - Sensenbrenner, James F. (U.S. House of Representatives, Wisc. Ninth Congressional District), 1980-1987 (Box 56)
  - Shamie, Ray (U.S. Senate, Mass.), 1985-1987 See also Container OV 5, Campaign poster (Box 56)
  - Siebens, Harold W., 1983-1986 For additional material see Container 42, National Citizen's Coalition (Box 57)
  - Siebert, Murial ("Mickie") (U.S. Senate, N.Y. Republican primary), 1982 (Box 57)
  - Smith, Denny (U.S. House of Representatives, Oreg. Second Congressional District) (Box 57)
    - "Denny Smith for Governor," 1994 (Box 57)
    - Direct mail, 1985-1988 (Box 57)
    - General, 1980-1990, (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - Issues book, 1988 (Box 57)
    - Media (Box 57)
      - Advertisements, 1984-1988 (Box 57)
      - General, 1980 (Box 57)
      - General, 1986-1988, (3 folders) (Box 58)
    - Military reform caucus, 1985-1986 (Box 58)
    - Miscellany, circa 1987 (Box 58)
    - News clippings, 1981-1988, (3 folders) (Box 58)
    - News clippings, 1981-1988 (Box 59)
    - Opposition research, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Oregonians Against Crime, 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - Quality of Service questionnaire, 1988 (Box 59)
    - Surveys/polls, 1982-1987 (Box 60)
    - Voter's pamphlet, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Smith, Doug (U.S. Senate, Wash. Republican primary), 1988 (Box 60)
  - Strake, George See Container 55, Republican Party of Texas (Box 60)
  - Suffolk County Republican Committee (New York), 1982-1989, (3 folders) (Box 60)
  - Suhadolnik, Gary (U.S. House of Representatives, Ohio Nineteenth Congressional District), 1985-1986 (Box 60)
  - Sweeney, Mac (U.S. House of Representatives, Tex. Fourteenth Congressional District), 1984-1986 (Box 60)
  - Swindell, Pat (U.S. House of Representatives, Ga.. Fourth Congressional District), 1984-1988 (Box 60)
  - Texas Foundation for Conservative Studies, 1981-1989 (Box 60)
  - Texas Foundation for Conservative Studies, 1981-1989, (4 folders) (Box 61)
  - Town of Islip Republican Committee (New York), 1986-1989, (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Town of Islip Republican Committee (New York), 1986-1989 (Box 62)
  - Western Co. of North America See Container 10, Chiles, Eddie (Box 62)
  - Wiedner, Harriet (U.S. House of Representatives, Calif. 42nd Congressional District), 1988
  - Wilson, Peggy (U.S. Senate, La.), 1996 (Box 62)
  - Wood, Bob (Member of Provincial Parliament, Canada), 1982-1984 For additional material see Container 5, Brown, Colin, (3 folders) (Box 62)
  - Wortley, George C. (U.S. House of Representatives, N.Y. Ninth Congressional District), 1980-1987 (Box 62)
- Alphabetical File, 1970-2019 (Box 62-109)
  The Alphabetical File contains a mix of Finkelstein's working files, correspondence, and a variety of topics primarily concerned with his professional life. The series is an expansion of a file arrangement managed by Finkelstein, though it is unclear whether these files were kept for AJF & Associates or personal use. Some noteworthy contents of this series feature material related to his board membership to the American Conservative Union and the libertarian consumer advocacy group Consumer Alert, AJF & Associates proposals, and the response by Finkelstein and friends to an article published by Boston Magazine that publicly outed him as gay. Notable correspondents and gathered subject material in this series includes John Terry Dolan, Joan Ferdinand, Jeane J. Kirkpatrick, Gerald "Gerry" Nicholls, and Roger Stone,. Also included are speeches, interviews, and articles written by Finkelstein.
  Material types include correspondence, news clippings, articles, and message books.
  Arranged alphabetically by name, organization, or subject. The file structure of the digital content maintained as received.
  - Ailloni-Charas, Dan, 1979-1984 (Box 62)
  - Airlines, 1978-1983, 1996-2003 (Box 62)
  - American Association of Political Consultants, 1984-1986, 1999 (Box 62)
  - American Conservative Union, 1983-1986, (3 folders) (Box 63)
  - The American Lobby, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - American Political Report, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
  - American Red Cross, 1991 (Box 64)
  - Americans for a Sound Foreign Policy, 1985 (Box 64)
  - Andrews, Jaye, 1987, 1994, (3 folders) (Box 64)
  - "Archie Bunker House," undated (Box 64)
  - Articles (Box 64)
    - About Finkelstein, 1979-2013, 2019, (2 folders) (Box 64)
    - By Finkelstein, 1970, 1973, 1981, 1971 (Box 65)
    - Mention Finkelstein, 1971, 1974, 1981-2013, (3 folders) (Box 65)
    - Miscellany, 1981-2003, (2 folders) (Box 65)
    - Miscellany, 1981-2003, (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - "That's Politics," 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - "A" miscellaneous, 1978-2001 (Box 66)
  - Bernstein, Ellen, 1985-1986 (Box 66)
  - Bills, 1980-1989, (6 folders) (Box 67)
  - Biography, circa 1980-2015, (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Bishirjian, Richard J., 1984, 1986, 1997-1999, 2008 (Box 68)
  - Boston Magazine, 1996 (Box 68)
  - Buckley, James Lane, 1979-1989, 2000 See also Container 5, Buckley, James Lane (Box 68)
  - Buckley, John, 1983-1984 (Box 68)
  - Bush, George W., 2004 (Box 68)
  - "B" miscellaneous, 1982-2004, (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - California Republican Party, 1984-1988 (Box 68)
  - Campaign management manual, circa 1980 (Box 69)
  - Candidate profiles, 1979-1988, 1992, 1994, 2012, (4 folders) (Box 69)
  - Cards, 1971-2003 (Box 69)
  - Clements, Bill Perry, 1987 (Box 70)
  - Client requests, 1980-1984 (Box 70)
  - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 2005 (Box 70)
  - Cofrin, Douglas, 1976, 1981-1985 (Box 70)
  - Committee for a Peaceful Transition to Democracy, 1989-1991 (Box 70)
  - Commonwealth Trading Company, Inc., 1988 (Box 70)
  - Competitive Enterprise Institute, 1987-1989 (Box 70)
  - Complaints, 1979-1992, 1997 (Box 70)
  - Conservative Party of New York State, 1986 (Box 70)
  - Consumer Alert, 1978 (Box 70)
  - Consumer Alert, 1979-1982, (7 folders) (Box 71)
  - Consumer Alert, 1983-1986, (7 folders) (Box 72)
  - Consumer Alert, 1986-1990, (8 folders) (Box 73)
  - Consumer Alert, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Contacts, undated See also OV 1-4, Rolodex cards, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Cornstein, David, 1993-1999 (Box 74)
  - Correspondence (unknown), 1980-1989, 1997-1998, 2003, 2010 (Box 74)
  - "C" miscellaneous, 1970-2002, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - D'Amato, Alphonse, 1994-2004 See also Container 14, D'Amato, Alphonse, (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - D'Amato, Armand, 1984-1989 (Box 75)
  - Daxon, Tom, 1980-1981 (Box 75)
  - DCi News, 1996 (Box 75)
  - Deaver, Michael, 1983-1985 (Box 75)
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1987 (Box 75)
  - Dioguardi, Joe, 1985-1988 (Box 75)
  - Direct mail examples, 1981-1989, 1999-2009, (2 folders) (Box 75)
  - Direct mail examples, 1981-1989, 1999-2009 (Box 76)
  - Diversified Research, Inc., 1983-1989 (Box 76)
  - Diversified Research, Inc., digital files, 1995, mss86414_221_001; mss86414_221_006; mss86414_221_008
  - Dolan, John Terrance ("Terry"), 1985-1987 See also Container 45, National Conservative Political Action Committee (Box 76)
  - The Dolan Report, 1984-1985, (3 folders) (Box 76)
  - Dole, Robert J., 1986-1987, 1996 (Box 76)
  - Dominican Republic, 1986 (Box 76)
  - "D" miscellaneous, 1979-1999 (Box 77)
  - East, John P., 1984-1986 (Box 77)
  - Election results, 1984-1988 (Box 77)
  - "E" miscellaneous, 1979-1997 (Box 77)
  - Ferdinand, Joan, 1984-2001 See also Container 12, Corcoran, Tom; Container 32, Koehler, Judy, (4 folders) (Box 77)
  - Ferdinand, Joan, 1984-2001, (3 folders) (Box 78)
  - Fisher, Anthony J., 1984-1985 (Box 78)
  - Foreign Affairs Research Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 78)
  - Foundation for American Entrepreneurship, 1985 (Box 78)
  - Francis, Michael, 1983-1986 (Box 78)
  - Fraser Institute, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 78)
  - Freedom Conservatives of America, 1983 (Box 78)
  - Fund for a Conservative Majority, 1980-1983 (Box 79)
  - "F" miscellaneous, 1979-2003 (Box 79)
  - Gaon, Boaz, 1997-2001 For additional material see Container 36, Likud; Container 81, Israel (Box 79)
  - Gallagher, Tom, 1982 (Box 79)
  - Gekas, George W., 1982-1983 (Box 79)
  - Gingrich, Newt, 1983-1987 (Box 79)
  - Goodman, Roy M., 1984-1985 (Box 79)
  - Gotlieb, Alan, 1983-1985 (Box 79)
  - Greenfield, N. Richard, 1982-1987, (2 folders) (Box 79)
  - Group for Good Government, 1973 (Box 79)
  - "G" miscellaneous, 1979-2001, (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Hauter, Robert, 1978-1982 (Box 80)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1981-1991 (Box 80)
  - Holland, Terrance, 1980 (Box 80)
  - Hosler, Karen, 1981 (Box 80)
  - Hotels, 1979-2002 (Box 80)
  - "H" miscellaneous, 1979-2001, (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Indiana State Republican Committee, 1983 (Box 80)
  - InstaPoll, 1983 (Box 80)
  - Interviews, 1996-2004 (Box 80)
  - Invitations, 1978-1981 (Box 80)
  - Invitations, 1982-2012, (4 folders) (Box 81)
  - Israel, 1979, 1981, 1996-2010 See also Container 36, Likud, (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - "I" miscellaneous, 1981-1987, 2002 (Box 81)
  - Jacobs, Richard (U.S. House of Representatives, Tenn. 8th congressional district), 1988 (Box 82)
  - Jewish community, 1981-1985 (Box 82)
  - Johnson, Sam (U.S. House of Representatives, Texas 3rd congressional district), 1991 (Box 82)
  - "J" miscellaneous, 1979-1999 (Box 82)
  - Kettler, Carl, 1981-1982 (Box 82)
  - Kiernan Mahoney & Associates, digital files, 1993-1996, mss86414_221_002; mss86414_221_003; mss86414_221_004; mss86414_221_005; mss86414_221_007; mss86414_221_008
  - King, Edward J., 1980, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Kingon, Alfred H., 1979-1985 (Box 82)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J., 1984-1987, (3 folders) (Box 82)
  - Klein, Barbara, 1985-1989 (Box 82)
  - Kudlow, Lawrence, 1979-1982 (Box 82)
  - "K" miscellaneous, 1979-2003 (Box 83)
  - Lavelle, Michael See Container 76, Diversified Research, Inc. (Box 83)
  - Lazio, Rick, 2000, 2010 (Box 83)
  - Learsy, Raymond, and Carol Learsy, 1979-1991, 1999 (Box 83)
  - Legal issues, 1982-1989, (4 folders) (Box 83)
  - Lehrman, Lewis, 1979-1982 (Box 83)
  - Loeb, William, 1979-1983 (Box 84)
  - "L" miscellaneous, 1979-2013 (Box 84)
  - Madison Square Garden, 2004 (Box 84)
  - Mahe, Eddie, Jr., 1983-1989 (Box 84)
  - Mahoney, J. Daniel, 1981-1985 (Box 84)
  - Mahoney, Kiernan See Container DF, Kiernan Mahoney and Associates (Box 84)
  - Marik, Robert, 1979-1981 (Box 84)
  - Marino, Ralph, 1981, 1989 (Box 84)
  - Marsh, Tony, 1985-1991 For additional material see Container 57, Smith, Denny (Box 84)
  - Martin, Robin, 1982-1991 (Box 84)
  - Martinez, Bob, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Maseng, Mari, 1980-1983 (Box 84)
  - Massachusetts Federation of Young Republicans, 1980-1981 (Box 84)
  - McConnell, Mitch, 1977-1989 (Box 84)
  - McLaughlin, John, 1980, 2017 (Box 84)
  - Moore, Robin, 1981 (Box 84)
  - Morello, John, 1981-1986 (Box 84)
  - Murphy/Powers Media Inc., 1978-1989, (2 folders) (Box 85)
  - "M" miscellaneous, 1976-2017, (2 folders) (Box 85)
  - Neese, Terry, 1986-1990 (Box 85)
  - Nelson, Avi, 1980-1988 (Box 85)
  - Nelson, Avi, 1980-1988, (2 folder) (Box 86)
  - Nelson, Laura, 1982-1985 (Box 86)
  - New Jersey Political Action Committee, 1981, 1987-1988 (Box 86)
  - New York Federal Political Action Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 86)
  - New York State Political Action Committee, 1976-1989, (3 folders) (Box 86)
  - New York State Political Action Committee, 1976-1989 (Box 87)
  - New York State Quarterly Report, 1981, (2 folders) (Box 87)
  - New York State Senate Republican Campaign Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 87)
  - New York Times, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
  - Newell, Briding, 1981-1984 (Box 87)
  - News clippings, 1979-2000 (Box 87)
  - Nicholls, Gerry, 1995-2009 (Box 87)
  - Nichols, Miller, 1980-1982 (Box 87)
  - Noble, Richard, 1984-1986 (Box 87)
  - "N" miscellaneous, 1980-1996, (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Ohioans to Stop Excessive Taxation, 1983 (Box 88)
  - Office miscellany, 1979-1990 (Box 88)
  - Ottosen, Karl, 1985-1987 (Box 88)
  - "O" miscellaneous, 1978-1989 (Box 88)
  - Paul, Barry, 1981-1983 (Box 88)
  - Paxon, L. William, 1987-1988 (Box 88)
  - Pearce, Steve, 2008, mss86414_221_009
  - Phone message books (Box 89)
    - 1985-1988, (6 vols.) (Box 89)
    - 1988-1989, (6 vols.) (Box 90)
    - 1989-1990, (6 vols.) (Box 91)
    - 1990-1991, (6 vols.) (Box 92)
    - 1991-1992, (6 vols.) (Box 93)
    - 1992-1993, (6 vols.) (Box 94)
    - 1993-1994, 1998, (7 vols.) (Box 95)
    - 2002-2004, (7 vols.) (Box 96)
    - 2004-2009, (6 vols.) (Box 97)
    - 2009-2013, (4 vols.) (Box 98)
  - Photographs, 1972-1986, 1995, 2004 See also OV 1-4, Richard Nixon thank you card (Box 98)
  - Pirro, Jeanine See Container DF, Kiernan Mahoney and Associates (Box 98)
  - The Political Report, 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box 98)
  - The Political Report, 1983-1985 (Box 99)
  - The Polling Report, 1985-1989 (Box 99)
  - Powers, Chris, 1983-1998 (Box 99)
  - Presidential Omnibus, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 99)
  - Pressler, Larry, 1996-2000 (Box 99)
  - Productivity Communication Center, 1983-1988 (Box 99)
  - Profit sharing plan, 2000-2004 (Box 99)
  - Proposals (Box 99)
    - American Association of Retired People, 1987 (Box 99)
    - Darden, George ("Buddy"), 1987 (Box 99)
    - General, 1979-1989 (Box 99)
    - General, 1979-1989, (6 folders) (Box 100)
    - Mason, Robert H., Jr., 1987 (Box 100)
    - National Right to Life Committee, 1979 (Box 100)
    - Potential clients, 1981-1988 (Box 100)
    - Price Bill, 1987-1989 (Box 101)
    - Puerto Rico Statehood Campaign, 1989 (Box 101)
    - Responses, 1981-1985 (Box 101)
    - Richardson, H. L., 1978 (Box 101)
    - Texas Rangers (baseball team), 1980-1988 See also Container 10, Chiles, Eddie (Box 101)
    - Vrdolyak, Edward R., 1987-1988 (Box 101)
  - Public Research, Syndicated, 1979-1980 (Box 101)
  - Pullen, Penny, 1984 (Box 101)
  - "P-Q" miscellaneous, 1978-1994, (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Reilly, Patrick, 1981-1985 (Box 101)
  - Republican Jewish Coalition, 2010 (Box 102)
  - Résumés, 1980-1995, (6 folders) (Box 102)
  - Résumés, 1980-1995, (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Ritchie, Steve, 1981-1983 (Box 103)
  - Rostad, Knut, 1985-1987 (Box 103)
  - Roybal, Tim, 1984-1988 (Box 103)
  - Rutkowski, Ed, 1987 (Box 103)
  - "R" miscellaneous, 1980-1996, (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Sannasardo Advertising Inc., 1979 (Box 103)
  - Seminar information, undated (Box 103)
  - Shaviv Strategy and Campaigns, circa 2010 (Box 103)
  - Shirley, Craig, 1979, 1987, 1999, 2007-2013 (Box 103)
  - Simms, Adam, 1983-1999 (Box 103)
  - Simons, Harold, 1980-1985 (Box 104)
  - Solicitations, 1981-1989, (5 folders) (Box 104)
  - Speaking engagements, 1983-1996, 2004, 1983-1993, 2004 (Box 105)
  - Speeches (Box 105)
    - By Finkelstein, 1981-1985, circa 2003, 2013 (Box 105)
    - By others, 1964, 1980-1984, 1992-2004, (2 folders) (Box 105)
  - Stop Hillary Now! See Container 70, Clinton, Hillary Rodham (Box 105)
  - Stone, Ann See same container, Stone, Roger (Box 105)
  - Stone, Roger, 1978-2000 (Box 105)
  - Survey expenses, 1978-1985 (Box 105)
  - Surveys/polls (Box 105)
    - European Union, 2016-2017 (Box 105)
    - European Union, 2016-2017, (2 folders) (Box 106)
    - Miscellany, 1989, 1993, 1996 (Box 106)
    - National polls, 1981-1989, 1996 (Box 106)
    - National polls, 1981-1989, 1996, (2 folders) (Box 107)
    - United States-Soviet relations, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Switzler, Roy, 1986 (Box 107)
  - "S" miscellaneous, 1979-1997, (2 folders) (Box 107)
  - Travel visas, 1991-1996 (Box 107)
  - Trueman, Patrick, 1984 (Box 108)
  - "T" miscellaneous, 1980-1989 (Box 108)
  - Uhlmann, John, 1984-1986, 1996, 2002 (Box 108)
  - "V" miscellaneous, 1982-1984, 1990 (Box 108)
  - Wallwork, Jim, 1984, 1991-1995 (Box 108)
  - Watts, George, 1983 (Box 108)
  - Weber, Vin, 1983-1984 (Box 108)
  - Welbourn, Jack, 1981-1982 (Box 108)
  - White, F. Clinton, 1992-1993 (Box 108)
  - Wolf, Diane, 1984-1987, 2005 (Box 108)
  - "W" miscellaneous, 1977-1999, (2 folders) (Box 108)
  - Yonkers, N.Y., 1989 (Box 108)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1983-1986 (Box 109)
  - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, 1981-1998, 2015-2017 (Box 109)
  - Zephyr Entertainment Partners, 1986 (Box 109)
- Travel and Itineraries File, 1983-2016 (Box 109-137)
  The Travel and Itineraries File contains Finkelstein's scheduling books, detailing trips and meetings.
  Material types include schedule books and itineraries.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1983 (Box 109)
  - 1984 (Box 109)
  - 1985 (Box 110)
  - 1986 (Box 110)
  - 1987 (Box 110)
  - 1988 (Box 111)
  - 1989 (Box 111)
  - 1990 (Box 111)
  - 1991 (Box 112)
  - 1992 (Box 112)
  - 1993, (3 folders) (Box 112)
  - 1994, (3 folders) (Box 113)
  - 1995, (2 folder) (Box 113)
  - 1995 (Box 114)
  - 1996, (4 folders) (Box 114)
  - 1997, (5 folders) (Box 115)
  - 1998, (4 folders) (Box 116)
  - 1999, (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - 1999 (Box 117)
  - 2000, (3 folders) (Box 117)
  - 2001 (Box 117)
  - 2001, (2 folders) (Box 118)
  - 2002, (3 folders) (Box 118)
  - 2003, (3 folders) (Box 119)
  - 2004, (2 folders) (Box 119)
  - 2004 (Box 120)
  - 2005, (4 folders) (Box 120)
  - 2005, (6 folders) (Box 121)
  - 2006, (6 folders) (Box 122)
  - 2006, (6 folders) (Box 123)
  - 2006, (3 folders) (Box 124)
  - 2007, (2 folders) (Box 124)
  - 2007, (5 folders) (Box 125)
  - 2007 (Box 126)
  - 2008, (3 folders) (Box 126)
  - 2008, (4 folders) (Box 127)
  - 2009 (Box 127)
  - 2009, (5 folders) (Box 128)
  - 2009 (Box 129)
  - 2010, (4 folders) (Box 129)
  - 2010, (5 folders) (Box 130)
  - 2011, (5 folders) (Box 131)
  - 2011, (3 folders) (Box 132)
  - 2012, (3 folders) (Box 132)
  - 2012, (5 folders) (Box 133)
  - 2013, (6 folders) (Box 134)
  - 2013 (Box 135)
  - 2014, (5 folders) (Box 135)
  - 2014 (Box 136)
  - 2015, (5 folders) (Box 136)
  - 2016, (5 folders) (Box 137)
- Personal File, 1960-2013 (Box 138-139)
  The Personal File contains a small collection of material concerning Finkelstein's college years and family. The most notable portion of this series includes writings, notes, and clippings from Finkelstein's time as an undergraduate at Queen's College, New York. The writings are of particular interest, containing poems and letters written by him and a classmate which reveal a brief glimpse as to how Finkelstein viewed himself at that time. Also included are papers related to his family.
  Material types include notes, letters, correspondence, articles, and news clippings.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material.
  - Conservative clubs, 1964-1970 (Box 138)